emagazines.com 2018-10-08

# Privacy Policy

**eMagazines.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: eMagazines.com

BY ACCESSING THIS SITE YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT.

**Email Communications**  
When you order a digital magazine and it is delivered by eMagazines, eMagazines will send you a courtesy confirmation. Each time a new issue is released you will also get an email notification from eMagazines. 

All communications will contain simple removal instructions.

**Information Automatically Logged**  
We use your IP address to help identify you and your account. 

**Cookies**  
Our Site uses cookies to keep track of your account. 

**Order Forms**  
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like your email address), unique identifiers (like your customer number), and demographic information (like your zip code). 

Contact information from the order forms is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Unique identifiers are collected from Web site visitors for use as account numbers in our record system.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. eMagazines.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. This site is tested and certified daily by hackersafe.com to pass the FBI/SANS Internet Security Test. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from our partners, and us. 

You can opt out by visiting in here and submitting the form or clicking unsubscribe on any email you receive from eMagazines.com. 

**Data Quality/Access**  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

You can click here and provide your updated information. 

**GDPR**  
This site is compliant with GDPR laws and regulations. User can edit, delete, freeze and view their personal information at this location GDPR or users can [click here](https://emagazines.zendesk.com/hc/en-use) and provide their updated information via a customer support ticket. Users can withdraw consent by deleting their account. A GDPR ID will be provided as a cancellation number. 

By accepting the Privacy Policy you are verifying that you are at least 16 years or older, or 13 years or older with parents' consent.

Data Retention: Data is kept until the data controllers request the data to be removed according to their policies.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

eMagazines  
230 West huron St.  
Ste 500  
Chicago, IL 60654 

Click here to contact support

Privacy Policy Updated: 2018.
